http://www.excelta.com/terms-and-conditions

0
Cart ( 0 )
0 items ( $0.00 )
View the Full Cart
ProductsUltra Precision Cobaltima® TweezersCutting TweezersTweezers (Forceps)Ultra Precision Cobaltima® TweezersExotic Metals/CoatingsConventional Style TweezersStraight Tapered - MicroscopyStraight Very Fine PointsStraight Semi-Fine PointsStraight Strong Points Straight Medium PointsStraight Broad PointsCurved Very Fine PointsAngled Very Fine PointsAngled Medium PointsAngled Flat Sharp PointsFlat Blunt PointsCutting TweezersErgonomic TweezersStraight Tapered - Microscopy Straight Very Fine PointsStraight Medium PointsTapered Flat Round Points Angled Very Fine Points Curved Very Fine Points Cleanroom SafeMiniature TweezersReverse Action TweezersSmall Parts Handling TweezersThru-HoleWire HandlingS.M.D. HandlingCeramic TweezersWafer Handling TweezersReplaceable Tip TweezersCarbon FiberAcetalCopolymerPeekPlastic TweezersKitsCuttersHard Wire CuttersSide CuttersHard Wire CuttersSmall CuttersMedium Head - 9200 SeriesMedium Cutters - 7000 SeriesLarge CuttersSpecialty CuttersAngled HeadLong Nose Fine TipTransverse EndCable & Tubing Cutters'Stand off' Shear CuttersLarge FrameSmall FramePliersMiniature NoseStandard PliersSmall NoseMedium NoseLarge NoseSpecialty PliersInsertion-ExtractionConcave-Convex NoseReplaceable Tip Soft NoseWide NoseCleanroom PliersLead Form & Cut PliersAnti-Shock Shear Cutters/FormersForming PliersLead BendingMultiple Lead FormerStress Relief FormerWire StrippersScissorsCarbide Insert ScissorsKevlar ScissorsHigh Precision ScissorsStandard ScissorsSelf Opening ScissorsLaboratory ScissorsBrushesSmall Hand ToolsOpticsPin VisesProbes, Scribes, Dotting PensRazor BladesScalpelsSpatulas/OilersTest EquipmentPocket BeeperRCL MeterVacuum ToolsBulbPen-VacElectricElectric (Roto-Pic)KitsSpare PartsLaboratory & Cleanroom InstrumentsTweezers (Forceps)Rongeurs CuttersCleanroom PliersLaboratory ScissorsHemostats/ClampsProbesScalpelsRazor BladesMisc. Lab ToolsDissection KitsJeweler's InstrumentsTweezersSide CuttersHard Wire CuttersSmall CuttersMedium Head - 9200 SeriesMedium Cutters - 7000 SeriesLarge CuttersStandard PliersSmall NoseMedium NoseLarge NoseScrewdriversEyebrow TweezersKitsOpportunity Buys
PRODUCTS
Tweezers & Forceps
Ultra Precision Cobalt
Exotic Metals/Coatings
Conventional Style Tweezers
Cutting Tweezers
Ergonomic Tweezers
Miniature Tweezers
Need Assistance?
We are here to help.Call 805.686.4686
Terms and Conditions
Terms and Conditions
Notice: If
your legitimate business is purchasing our products for RESALE – Please contact sales@excelta and
ask for our Web sales Partnering Program Retail
Application. If approved, you may be eligible for additional discounts and
promotions.
Last updated: February 25, 2019
Please read these Terms and
Conditions ("Terms", "Terms and Conditions") carefully
before using the https://www.excelta.com/
website (the "Service")
operated by Excelta Corporation ("us", "we", or
"our").
Your access to and use of the
Service is conditioned upon your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms.
These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who wish to access or use
the Service.
By accessing or using the
Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of
the terms then you do not have permission to access the Service.
Purchases
If you wish to purchase any
product or service made available through the Service ("Purchase"),
you may be asked to supply certain information relevant to your Purchase
including, without limitation, your credit card number, the expiration date of
your credit card, your billing address, and your shipping information.
You represent and warrant that:
(i) you have the legal right to use any credit card(s) or other payment
method(s) in connection with any Purchase; and that (ii) the information you
supply to us is true, correct and complete.
The service may employ the use
of third party services for the purpose of facilitating payment and the
completion of Purchases. By submitting your information, you grant us the right
to provide the information to these third parties subject to our Privacy
Policy.
We reserve the right to refuse
or cancel your order at any time for reasons including but not limited to:
product or service availability, errors in the description or price of the
product or service, error in your order or other reasons.
We reserve the right to refuse
or cancel your order if fraud or an unauthorized or illegal transaction is
suspected.
Availability, Errors and
Inaccuracies
We are constantly updating
product and service offerings on the Website. We may experience delays in
updating information on the Website and in our advertising on other web sites.
The information found on the website may contain errors or inaccuracies and may
not be complete or current. Products or services may be mispriced, described
inaccurately, or unavailable on the website and we cannot guarantee the
accuracy or completeness of any information found on the website.
We therefore reserve the right
to change or update information and to correct errors, inaccuracies, or
omissions at any time without prior notice.
Accounts
When you create an account with
us, you guarantee that you are above the age of 18, and that the information
you provide us is accurate, complete, and current at all times. Inaccurate,
incomplete, or obsolete information may result in the immediate termination of
your account on the Service.
You are responsible for
maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password, including but not
limited to the restriction of access to your computer and/or account. You agree
to accept responsibility for any and all activities or actions that occur under
your account and/or password, whether your password is with our Service or a
third-party service. You must notify us immediately upon becoming aware of any
breach of security or unauthorized use of your account.
You may not use as a username
the name of another person or entity that is not lawfully available for use, a
name or trademark that is subject to any rights of another person or entity
other than you, without appropriate authorization. You may not use as a
username any name that is offensive, vulgar or obscene.
We reserve the right to refuse
service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in our
sole discretion.
Intellectual Property
The website and its original
content, features and functionality are and will remain the exclusive property
of Excelta Corporation and its licensors. The website is protected by
copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the United States and foreign
countries. Our trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with
any product or service without the prior written consent of Excelta
Corporation.
Links To Other Web Sites
Our website may contain links
to third party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by Excelta
Corporation.
Excelta Corporation has no
control over, and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies,
or practices of any third party web sites or services. We do not warrant the
offerings of any of these entities/individuals or their websites.
You acknowledge and agree that
Excelta Corporation shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly,
for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with
use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or
through any such third party web sites or services.
We strongly advise you to read
the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third party web sites or
services that you visit.
Termination
We may terminate or suspend
your account and bar access to the website immediately, without prior notice or
liability, under our sole discretion, for any reason whatsoever and without
limitation, including but not limited to a breach of the Terms.
If you wish to terminate your
account, you may simply discontinue using the website.
All provisions of the Terms
which by their nature should survive termination shall survive termination,
including, without limitation, ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers,
indemnity and limitations of liability.
Governing Law
These Terms shall be governed
and construed in accordance with the laws of California, United States, without
regard to its conflict of law provisions.
Our failure to enforce any
right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those
rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable
by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect.
These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service,
and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have had between us
regarding the Service.
Changes
We reserve the right, at our
sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is
material we will provide at least 15 days notice prior to any new terms taking
effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole
discretion.
By continuing to access or use
our Service after any revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the
revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, you are no longer
authorized to use the Service.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about
these Terms, please contact us.
Returns and Refunds Policy
Thank you for shopping at
Excelta Corporation.
If you are not entirely
satisfied with your purchase, we're here to help.
Excelta must be notified within
15 days of shipment/invoice date of any errors or shortages. If notification is
not made within 15 days and an RMA subsequently issued, Excelta will not assume
liability for errors in shipment.
Our products can be returned
within 30 days of the original purchase of the product. A new product may be
exchanged for another product or returned for a refund. All returns for credit
are at the discretion of Excelta.
To be eligible for a return,
please make sure that:
You obtained a Return Merchandise Number (RMA) from us; (1-866-EXCELTA or email
sales@excelta)
•
Failure to obtain an RMA# may result in your shipment being returned to you,
not accepted at delivery and credits denied. RMA #’s are valid for 15 days
after issue date.
•
Requests for RMA’s MUST be placed within 30 days of Excelta’s invoice date for
all quality issues.
• NO warranty is implied for
misused or abused tools; Acceptance of any quality issue return is at
the discretion of Excelta is subject to Quality Control Inspection prior to
credit being approved.
• Products under this policy
may not be returned for any reason after 60 days.
Factory ReNewed Products
• Factory ReNewed products are limited to a 30 day return period.
Products that do not meet these
criteria will not be considered for return.
To obtain a Return Merchandise
Number (RMA), contact us:
•
By phone number: 805-686-4686
• By email: sales@excelta.com
Send the product with its
original packing and the receipt or proof of purchase and the RMA number, along
with a note indicating whether you want to exchange the product (and if so,
what other product you want to order) or a refund, to:
Excelta Corporation Attention:
connection with the return of a product are non-refundable.
You are responsible for paying
the costs of shipping and for the risk of loss of or damage to the product
during shipping, both to and from Excelta Corporation.
Damaged items
If you received a damaged
product, please notify us immediately for assistance. See ‘Returns and Refunds
Policy’ for instructions.
Custom (Specials) items
Unfortunately, custom items
cannot be returned or refunded. Only regular price items can be refunded.
Contact us
If you have any questions about
our Returns and Refunds Policy, please contact us:
•
By phone number: 805-686-4686
• By email: sales@excelta.com
Privacy Policy
Effective date: February 25,
2019
Excelta Corporation
("us", "we", or "our") operates the
https://www.excelta.com website (hereinafter referred to as the
"Service"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the
collection, use and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and
the choices you have associated with that data.
We use your data to provide and
improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use
of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this
Privacy Policy, the terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as
in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://www.excelta.com
Definitions
• Service
Service is the
https://www.excelta.com website operated by Excelta Corporation
• Personal Data
Personal Data means data about
a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and
other information either in our possession or likely to come into our
possession).
• Usage Data
Usage Data is data collected
automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service
infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
• Cookies
Cookies are small files stored
on your device (computer or mobile device).
Information Collection and
Use
We collect several different
types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to
you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may
ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can
be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally
identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
on how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage
Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address
(e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that
you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages,
unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar
tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and we hold certain
information.
Cookies are files with a small
amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are
sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Other tracking
technologies are also used such as beacons, tags and scripts to collect and
track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser
to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if
you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our
Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
• Session
Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
• Preference
Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various
settings.
• Security Cookies. We
use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
Excelta Corporation uses the collected
data for various purposes:
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you
choose to do so
•
To provide customer support
•
To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
Personal Data, may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located
outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction
where the data protection laws may differ from those of your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside
United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we
transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it
there.
Your consent to this Privacy
Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your
agreement to that transfer.
Excelta Corporation will take
all the steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely
and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal
Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate
controls in place including the security of your data and other personal
information.
Disclosure of Data
Disclosure for Law
Enforcement
Under certain circumstances,
Excelta Corporation may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required
to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a
court or a government agency).
Legal Requirements
Excelta Corporation may
disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is
necessary to:
•
To comply with a legal obligation
•
To protect and defend the rights or property of Excelta Corporation
•
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
important to us but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet
or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use
commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot
guarantee its absolute security.
Our Policy on "Do Not
Track" Signals under the California Online Protection Act (CalOPPA)
We do not support Do Not Track
("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser
to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.
You can enable or disable Do
Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.
Service Providers
We may employ third party
companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service
Providers"), provide the Service on our behalf, perform Service-related
services or assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access
to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are
obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Payments
We may provide paid products
and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services
for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).
We will not store or collect
your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our
third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is
governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the
standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council,
which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and
Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment
information.
The payment processors we work
with are:
to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click a third party link,
you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to
review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and
assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any
third party sites or services.
Children's Privacy
Our Service does not address
anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").
We do not knowingly collect
personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are
a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Child has provided us with
Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected
Personal Data from children
without verification of
parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Changes to This Privacy
Policy
We may update our Privacy
Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new
Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email
and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming
effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy
Policy.
You are advised to review this
Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are
effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about
this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
• By email: danielg@excelta.com
